This is today's top picks.
Where should you keep your eyes on today's session? Shortly
after, we will continue the series of budget picks that
we had stolen yesterday. Today
also we have to take budget picks by choosing from two experts from the spinal.
First, I will take
Munir, who is keeping an eye on Mayuresh, what is he
expecting in the budget,
and which stock is fundamentally the
most preferred in that space. Secondly,
you had given a good position trade,
today it is Manas's turn. By the way, it was Manas's turn on
Monday, I forgot Manas, you did
not bring that day today, so sorry, whatever Manas has brought today, I will
go to Manas, two budget related picks shortly,
but you are starting
with today's stock news and three
important numbers of the futures market will come
and all three came after the market closed yesterday, in
which the first two are insurance players, I will
start with them, the
numbers of ICICI Prudential and ICICI Lombard, the
numbers of Potential Life Insurance.
Q3 year on year new business premium has
jumped by 3/4%. Value of New
Business (C&C) 20%
VNB margins have
increased from 26.7% to
33.9%, showing an improvement of 720 basis points.
Well, these results are being said lazily,
its premium is better than expectations,
its up, its Value of New
Business (VNB) margins
are better than substitution and the strong improvement is being
seen on machines. Sir, please ask for
its portfolio mix. If you ask for the
product mix, then the margin
of the protection business's
fraction in the mix is ​​increasing.
ICICI Pro is getting the benefit of it. We have
taken the trade of ICICI Pro with Manas
since last year and there has been a good bullish pickup continuously.
Look at the place of ICICI Pro on Manas charts, very good patterns are being formed,
consistent outperformance is being seen.
We
saw it yesterday and I believe that
you can see a good rally in the current evapse also.
Yesterday only my combination was not there and  I
think you should still
carry it straight, a target of up to ₹500
is possible and if you did not buy it yesterday then you can buy it today also,
you can have the stock at 478 and the first
target will be 492 and then it is possible to buy the tyres at up to ₹500,
ICICI has become the proof,
okay this is ICICI, we had
created a good position before the results, the momentum was
seen to be building up well, we are not disappointed with the numbers
and the wood is in the mood even after the numbers, the
traction momentum may be seen
continuing,
yesterday we saw this in Davos